Hello um today we will be discussing
about sun accelerate This is one of the
best product of Sun Life um so 20 years
20 year endowment life insurance product
So this is not 20 years to pay but the
maturity is um 20 years it is call accel
8 because it is only 8 years to pay so
life insurance coverage has increased
cash benefits have also increased and
there is a guaranteed maturity benefit
with special bonus and Dividend earning
and limited payment period which is only
8 years so for this
example
um 30 years old female non-smoker
her premium will be
52,000 which is
Php5 a year and total disability benefit
waver of premium of
php650 per year Why money back guarantee
because um the total paid by the client
within 8 years is 4
4,480 and
what she can get After 20
years is a here in the total living benefit
that is seen
um what she can earn is
72,000
and
976  and this is ah not the guaranteed
figure  because that's why it started like this,
it started to [ __ ], this is the accumulated benefit,
so for example, the client will take
his benefits
from when the paying
period ends in the 8th year, so 20k, so that won't
accumulate because he already took it,
so next, after 2 years, 25k, after 2
years, 30k, after 3 years, 35k, that's it,
so the total of
all that will
be + 95
+ 65 +
45, so the total of all
that will be
2,45,000, when
45, when all the cash outs are added,
he didn't wait to
withdraw, so that's
25,000 as opposed
to letting him keep
the accumulated endowment benefit in the company,
it's possible that it will become his income, which is
32,798, so the difference
if he just stays in the company and
lets it grow, is
57,395, that's what he can lose, so
again  endowment benefit is guaranteed
the accumulated endowment benefit is
this It depends on the percentage that
the company gives so so here in the proposal
you can see that the
accumulation rate is 4 4.2% but
according to our Branch Manager now
it is around
4.6% the accumulated benefit so
the rate is
higher um and again aside from
from the um guaranteed endowment benefit
Sun Life still gives a
Dividend
So this is
also um not
guaranteed but Once Sun
Life earns it will give to
its policy holders So for dis regard um
it starts when the client is 39 because the
client is age 30 female when
she started taking so when she is 39 years old
Sun Life will give something
possible um so That's 7240 a year
next year until Ayun until
year 20 so you can also
withdraw this Once it starts
giving Dividend or you can also
um stay in Sun Life and earn too
So there you go you didn't take it
possible with
12,000  You have a withdrawal at
maturity So if you will
um once this um policy matures what
you can possibly get is a total
of
722 976 so it is a money back guarantee
so this guaranteed cash value is included in this
Yes all of that will also be given and what
you have saved in the endowment this
Dividend you have saved and if there is
any accumulated special paid up bonus
so the total will be 722 976
roughly as opposed to what the
client paid which is 414
480,000 so around
8,400 will be the profit over the 8
years that you are paying um and of course
while you are paying for that 20 years
you are also insured so this um insurance started
at
250k um by The End of maturity it is 1 million
So this is a winwin plan which
is called the sun accelerate plan for
more questions just send me a pm Thank
you
stop